Sometimes, good events can change us.
For example, someone might try a skateboard and become someone who loves excitement.
These people might also like roller coasters or skydiving when they grow up.
At the same time, other people might feel something different about skateboarding.
They get on the skateboard and like trying to do a kickflip.
They don't just like the skateboarding because it's exciting, they like it because they enjoy
the challenge.
After skateboarding, they might want to learn something new, like playing guitar, a new
language or roll blocks.
For others, good events are about people.
Being with people who love us make us feel safe and like we belong.
No matter why we like something, the more we do these good things, the more they become
part of who we are.